Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  - KRAFT TELEVISION THEATER
    - Episode #545 The Girl Who Saw Too Much Robert Shaw, 1956 Aug 29 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Episode #553 Ten Grapefruit to Lisbon Frank D. Gilroy, 1956 Oct 24 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Time Lock Arthur Hailey, 1956 Nov 28 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - The Just and the Unjust Don and Katrina Ettlinger, 1956 Dec 26 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Most Blessed Woman (tentative) (2 copies) Wendell Mayes, 1957 Jan 23 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - The Discoverers (no author indicated), 1957 Feb 6 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - A Traveler from Brussels Jowl Ross, 1957 Feb 27 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Duel (no author indicated), 1957 Mar 6 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Collision Norman Vane, 1957 Mar 13 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - The Medallion Dale Wasserman, 1957 Apr 3 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - A Matter of Life Oliver Crawford, 1957 Apr 17 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - A Night of Rain (no author indicated), 1957 Apr 24 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Drummer Man Mel Goldberg, 1957 May 1 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Flesh and Blood Anthony Spinner, 1957 May 8 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Men of Prey (no author indicated), 1957 May 22 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - The Roaring Twentieth Calvin Tomkins, 1957 Jun 5 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Nothing Personal John Whedon, 1957 Jun 19 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - A Curly-Headed Kid Kavid Davidson, 1957 Jun 26 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - The Long Flight De Witt Copp, 1957 Jul 3 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Welcome to a Stranger Burton and James Benjamin, 1957 Jul 24 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Sextuplets John H. Morrin, 1957 Aug 7 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Ride into Danger Fred Edge Bob Van Scoyk, 1957 Aug 21 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Triumph (no author indicated), 1957 Sep 4 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - The Old Ticker John Whedon, 1957 Sep 11 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Vengeance Joseph Cochran, 1957 Sep 25 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Barefoot Soldier (no author indicated), 1957 Oct 2 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Smart Boy Harry W. Junkin, 1957 Oct 9 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - The Sound of Trouble Jack Paritz, 1957 Nov 20 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Heroes Walk on Sand George E. Dyslin, 1957 Dec 11 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Polka (2 copies) Robert J. Crean, 1957 Dec 18 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - The Other Wise Man Robert J. Crean, 1957 Dec 25 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - The Battle for Wednesday Night Bob Van Scoyk, 1958 Jan 1 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - The Velvet Trap David Davidson, 1958 Jan 8 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Code of the Corner Jack Klugman, 1958 Jan 15 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Eddie Sam Dann, 1958 Jan 22 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Run Joe Run James Lee Barrett, 1958 Jan 29 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Material Witness Henry Denker, 1958 Feb 19 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Man in Authority Marc Brandel, 1958 Apr 2 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - A Nugget from the Sunrise Jess Gregg, undated (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - All Those Beautiful Girls (no author indicated), undated (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Babies for Sale Norman Katkov, undated (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Bedroom 12 on the Appalachian Waterfall Harry Muheim, undated (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Box Seven-O-Four James Leo Herlihy, undated (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Boy in a Case Paul Monash, undated (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - The Category is Murder George Harmon Coxe, undated (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - The Diamond as Big as the Ritz William Hodapp (F. Scott Fitzgerald), undated (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Dollars to Doughnuts Judith Parrish, undated (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Fire and Ice Richard Fielder, undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Five Minutes to Choose Palmer Thompson, undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - The Gentle Grafter Dale Wasserman, undated (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Give Me the Courage Frances O'Neil, undated (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Good Old Charley Faye David Karp, undated (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Hang Up My Guns Wendell Mayes, undated (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Haunted Richard Carlson, undated (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - I am Fifteen--and I Don't Want to Die Christine Arnothy, undated (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - In the La Banza Samuel Elkin, undated (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - The Life of Mickey Mantle Nicholas E. Baehr, undated (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - The Long Arm George Faulkner, undated (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - The Man on Rollerskates Louis Pelletier, undated (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Mock Trial (no author indicated), undated (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - The Murder of a Sand Flea James Lee Barrett, undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - The Night of May Third Robert J. Shaw, undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - No Riders Wendell Mayes, undated (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Only a Rose Jack Paritz, undated (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Paper Foxhole James Elward, undated (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - The Plunge Grace Garment, undated (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Private Justice Edith and Samuel Grafton, undated (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - The Spell of the Tigress Michael Dyne, undated (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Spur of the Moment Oliver Crawford, undated (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Starfish William Noble, undated (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Teddy Bear (2 copies) James Lee Barrett, undated (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - The Wicked Have Waited Peter Lind Hayes Robert J. Crean, undated (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - The Wife of the Witness (fragment) Nelson Gidding, undated (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Fragments: (undated, no author) Albert Knight in a Business Suit The Night Watchers (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - LAMP UNTO MY FEET
    Religious CBS
    From years 1953, 1958, and 1961-64.
    Producers: Don Kellerman
    Directors: James MacAllen, Prentiss Childs, Neal Finn, Ted Holmes, Marvin Silbersher, Pamela Ilott, Robert Myhrum, Joe Clement
    Writers: Palmer Thompson, Donald Segall, Paul Tripp, Tom Rothfield, Richard Aurelio, Stephan Chodorov, Robert Crean, Arthur Mazzeo, Roman Brandstaetter, Jan Hartman, Robert Lucas, Fred Halliday, John Masefield, Henry Walsh, James Elward, David Ebin
    - 1953 Mar 8 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - 1953 Mar 15 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - 1953 Mar 22 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - 1953 Apr 5 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - 1953 Apr 12 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - 1953 Apr 19 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - 1953 Apr 26 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - 1953 May 3 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Mar 23 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Mar 30 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Oct 12 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - 1961 Jun 25 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - 1961 Oct 22 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - 1962 Jan 28 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - 1962 Feb 11 (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - 1962 Mar 11 (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - 1962 Apr 1 (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - 1962 Jun 24 (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - 1962 Oct 7 (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - 1962 Oct 14 (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - 1962 Nov 25 (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - 1963 Jan 13 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - 1963 Apr 28 (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - 1963 May 19 (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - 1963 Jun 30 (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - 1963 Jul 7 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - 1963 Aug 1 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - 1963 Oct 13 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - 1963 Nov 24 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - 1963 Dec 8 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - 1964 Jan 19 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Fragment (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - THE LARRY STORCH SHOW
    Producer: Al Span
    Directors: Frank Satinstein, Burt Shevelove
    Writers: Leo Solomon, Will Glickman, Joe Stein, Phil Sharp
    - 1953 Aug 1 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - 1953 Sep 5 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - LEGACY OF LIGHT
    Religious
    - I am the Lord thy God Goethe (Faust), 1961 Dec (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - LET'S TAKE A TRIP
    Travel documentary
    Producer: Stephen Fleischman
    Directors: Roger Englander, Tim Kiley
    Writers: Selig Alkon, Craig Gilbert
    - 1956 April 1 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - 1956 Apr 15 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - 1957 Jan 20 (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - LIFE WITH FATHER
    Producer: Fletcher Markle
    Directors: John Claar, William H. Brawn, Fletcher Markle, Peter Tewksbury
    Writers: William Roberts, Harry Kronman, Whitfield Cook, Brainerd Duffield, Dorothy Baker, Robert W. Russell
    (About half are dated, and the other half have the designation "Fil #" with no date indication. The former are listed first by date, and then the latter by number--these appear to be from the end of 1954 and beginning of 1955.)
    - 1953 Nov 22 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - 1954 Aug 31 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - 1954 Sep 14 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - 1954 Sep 21 (2 copies) (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - 1954 Oct 12 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - 1954 Nov 2 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - 1954 Dec 7 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - 1954 Dec 14 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - 1955 Jan 18 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - 1955 Jan 25 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Episode #1 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Episode #9 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Episode #11 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Episode #12 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Episode #13 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Episode #14 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Episode #18 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Episode #19 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Episode #20 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Episode #20 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Episode #23 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Episode #24 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Episode #25 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Episode #26 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - fragment (Box 198, Folder 19)
  - THE LINEUP
    Crime drama, based on San Francisco Police Dept. files
    Writers: David Dortort, Blake Edwards, Sidney Marshall, Leonard Lee, E. Jack Neuman, Sidney Morse, Whitfield Cook, Lawrence Resner, Stuart Jerome, Norman Jacob, Leonard Heideman, Lou Morheim, D. D. Beauchamp, William Spier, Ellis Marcus, Joseph Calvelli, Montgomery Pittman, Ed Waters, Fred Eggers, Joe Petracca
    (No dates are indicated--scripts appear to be from 1954-1956--and filing is by show number. There are several copies of most scripts; number of copies is indicated by a number in parentheses after each listing.)
    - Episode #29 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Episode #30 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Episode #31 (2 copies) (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Episode #32 (3 copies) (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Episode #35 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Episode #36 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Episode #37 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Episode #38 (2 copies) (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Episode #40 (2 copies) (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Episode #41 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Episode #43 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Episode #44 (2 copies) (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Episode #45 (2 copies) (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Episode #46 (3 copies) (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Episode #47 (3 copies) (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Episode #48 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Episode #49 (2 copies) (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Episode #50 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Episode #51 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Episode #52 (2 copies) (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Episode #54 (2 copies) (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Episode #56 (2 copies) (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Episode #57 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Episode #58 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Episode #59 (2 copies) (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Episode #60 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Episode #61 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Episode #62 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Episode #63 (2 copies) (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Episode #64 (2 copies) (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Episode #65 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Episode #66 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Episode #67 (3 copies) (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Episode #68 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Episode #69 (3 copies) (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Episode #70 (2 copies) (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Episode #71 (2 copies) (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Episode #72 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Episode #73 (2 copies) (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Episode #74 (2 copies) (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Episode #75 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Episode #76 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Episode #77 (3 copies) (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Episode #78 (2 copies) (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Episode #79 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Episode #80 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Episode #81 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Episode #82 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Episode #83 (2 copies) (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Episode #84 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Episode #85 (3 copies) (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Episode #86 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Episode #87 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Episode #88 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Episode #89 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Episode #90 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Episode #91 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Episode #92 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Episode #93 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Episode #94 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Episode #95 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Episode #96 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Episode #97 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Episode #98 (2 copies) (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Episode #99 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Episode #100 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Episode #101 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Episode #102 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Episode #103 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Episode #105 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Episode #106 (2 copies) (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Episode #107 (2 copies) (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Episode #109 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Episode #110 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Episode #113 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Episode #114 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Episode #115 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Davis Murder Case (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Dial 116 The Mafia Gang (2 copies) (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Girl Safecrackers (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Roberts Market Robbery (2 copies) (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - The Wildcat Case (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - (no title) (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - (no title) (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - LOOK UP AND LIVE
    Producer: Carl Beier
    Directors: Marvin Silbersher, Jack Kuney, Tim Kiley, R. F. Siemanowski, Robert Myhrum, Chalmers Dale, Joe Chomyn, Ted Holmes, Portman Paget, Erwin Nicholson, Roger Enblander, Bruce Minnix, Martin Carr
    (Writer is listed after each program, when possible)
    - Paul Roche, translator (Sophocles), 1956 Nov 11 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Ernest Kinoy, 1959 Apr 5 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - David Ebin, 1959 Apr 12 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Samuel J. Citron, 1959 Dec 6 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Samuel J. Citron, 1959 Dec 13 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - David Ebin, 1960 Jan 31 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Kenneth Cameron, 1961 Jul 9 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Slawomir Mrozek, 1961 Jul 16 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Al Meglin, 1961 Jul 23 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Albert Camus, 1961 Aug 13 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Samuel Elikin, 1961 Oct 29 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - David Ebin, 1961 Dec 3 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - David Ebin, 1961 Dec 10 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Ruth Newton, 1961 Dec 17 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - John Bloch, 1962 Jan 7 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - John Bloch, 1962 Jan 14 (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - 1962 Jan 21 (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - John Bloch, 1962 Jan 28 (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - Lee Hays, 1962 May 6 (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - Leo Brady, 1962 Jun 3 (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - Lee Hays (Herman Melville), 1962 Aug 26 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Joe Clement, 1962 Sep 9 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Lee Hays, 1962 Sep 30 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Stephan Chodorov, 1962 Oct 7 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - R. F. Siemanowski, 1962 Oct 14 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Lee Hays, 1962 Oct 21 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - R. F. Siemanowski, 1962 Oct 28 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - R. F. Siemanowski, 1962 Nov 4 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Carmen de Gaszto (?), 1963 Jan 6 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - 1963 Jan 13 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - 1963 Jan 20 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - 1963 Jan 27 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Craig Gilbert, 1963 Feb 10 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Jan Hartman, 1963 Mar 3 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Jan Hartman, 1963 Mar 10 (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Al Meglin, 1963 Jul 14 (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - James Elward, 1963 Jul 21 (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - James Elward, 1963 Jul 28 (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Al Meglin, 1963 Aug 4 (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - James Elward, 1963 Aug 11 (Box 208, Folder 20)
    - David Ebin, 1963 Sep 8 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - D. L. Ralph, 1963 Sep 22 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Craig Gilbert, 1963 Oct 6 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Craig Gilbert, 1963 Oct 13 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Craig Gilbert, 1963 Oct 20 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Craig Gilbert, 1963 Oct 27 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - J. F. Powers, 1963 Nov 10 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - William Jenkins, 1963 Nov 24 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - David Ebin, 1963 Dec 29 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Paul Claudel, undated (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - undated (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - LOVE STORY
  - LOVE STORY
    Producer: Richard Sandwick
    Director: David Heilweil
    - The Worst Christmas Story Sam Hall (Christopher Morley), 1953 Dec 25 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - LUCKY STRIKE THEATER
  - LUX VIDEO THEATER
    Directors: Buzz Kulik, Earl Ebi, Dick Goode, George Roy Hill, David O. McDearmon, Fred Carney, Norman Morgan, James Yarbrough
    - Autumn Nocturne Anne Howard Bailey, 1953 Feb 23 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - The Brooch William Faulkner, 1953 Mar (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - With Glory and Honor S. Lee Pogostin, 1953 Apr 9 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Put it in Feelsville Harry W. Junkin, 1953 Apr 16 (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Long Distance Miriam Hopkins, 1953 Apr 23 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Listen, He's Proposing Patricia Joudry, 1953 May 7 (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - The Ascent of Alfred Fishkettle Francis Bethencourt, 1953 Apr (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - The Betrayers Charles L. Emmons, 1953 May 14 (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - Tunnel Job Carey Wilber, 1953 May 21 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Ten Days to Forever Anne Howard Bailey, 1953 Jun 4 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Make Believe Bride Anne Howard Bailey, 1953 Jun 11 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Wind on the Way Seymour Stern, 1953 Jun 18 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - This is Jimmy Merrill Bernard Drew, 1953 Jun 25 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Force of Circumstance Harry W. Junkin, 1953 Jul 2 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - A Man in the Kitchen Leslie Waller, 1953 Jul 23 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - The Odyssey of Jeffrey Sewell Jerome Brandfield, 1953 Jul 30 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Hold Back the Dawn (no author indicated), 1954 Sep 16 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - The Heiress (no author indicated), 1954 Sep 23 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Meet Jo Cathcart John McGreevey, 1954 Sep 30 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - The Mansion Anne Howard Bailey, 1954 Oct 7 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Five Star Final (no author indicated), 1954 Nov 11 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Craig's Wife Sanford Barnett, 1954 Dec 2 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Ladies in Retirement Richard P. McDonagh, 1954 Dec 9 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - So Evil My Love S. H. Barnett, 1955 Jan 27 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - One Foot in Heaven S. H. Barnett, 1955 Feb 3 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Casablanca S. H. Barnett, 1955 Mar 3 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - It Grows on Trees John Wheedon, 1955 Mar 17 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Shadow of a Doubt Benjamin Simcoe, 1955 Mar 24 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - An Act of Murder S. H. Barnett, 1955 Apr 21 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - The Great McGinty S. H. Barnett, 1955 Apr 28 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Remember the Night S. H. Barnett, 1955 May 5 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Thunder on the Hill S. H. Barnett, 1955 May 26 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Inside Story John Whedon, 1955 Jun 16 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - The Creaking Gate Charles Bennett, 1955 Jul 7 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Dark Tribute Benjamin Simcoe, 1955 Jul 14 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Desperate Glory Joseph Cochran, 1955 Jul 21 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - The Bride Came C.O.D. S. H. Barnett, 1955 Jul 28 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - The Nine-Penny Dream Don M. Mankiewicz, 1955 Aug 4 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Perilous Deception Catherine Turney, 1955 Aug 11 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Nor All Your Tears Charles Bennett, 1955 Aug 18 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - June Bride S. H. Barnett, 1955 Aug 25 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - The Happy Man Raphael Hayes, 1955 Sep 8 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - The Lucky Finger (no author indicated), 1955 Sep 15 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - The Eyes of Father Tomasino Edwin Blum, 1955 Sep 22 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - The Amazing Mrs. Holliday (no author indicated), 1955 Oct 6 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - The Human Jungle Benjamin Simcoe, 1955 Oct 20 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - The Lady Gambler Leo Lieberman, 1955 Oct 27 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Appointment for Love S. H. Barnett, 1955 Nov 3 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Bedtime Story James Allardice, 1955 Nov 10 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - The Hunted S. H. Barnett, 1955 Nov 17 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Miss Suzie Slagle's James Allardice, 1955 Nov 24 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - The Web Harry Kronman, 1955 Dec 1 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Suspicion S. H. Barnett, 1955 Dec 8 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Just Across the Street S. H. Barnett, 1956 Jan 10 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Hired Wife Benjamin Simcoe, 1956 Jan 19 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Witness to Murder (no author indicated), 1956 Jan 26 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - The Green Promise Ed. James, 1956 Feb 2 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - The Star Katherine & Dale Eunson, 1956 Feb 9 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Night Song S. H. Barnett, 1956 Feb 16 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Here Comes the Groom Ed. James, 1956 Mar 1 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - The Criminal Code S. H. Barnett, 1956 Mar 8 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Tabloid S. H. Barnett, 1956 Apr 5 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - I Married a Stranger Herbert Abbott Spiro, 1956 Apr 19 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Has Anybody Seen My Gal Ed James, 1956 May 3 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Princess O'Rourke S. H. Barnett, 1956 May 17 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Indiscreet Mortimer Braus, 1956 May 31 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - She Married Her Boss S. H. Barnett, 1956 Jun 7 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - A House of His Own Loring Mandel, 1956 Jun 14 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - The Corrigan Case (2 copies) S. H. Barnett, 1956 Jun 21 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Yankee Cousin Benjamin Simcoe, 1956 Jun 28 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Sting in the Tail Stanley H. Silverman, 1956 Jul 12 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - The Captives Betty Ulius, 1956 Jul 19 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - The Wayward Saint Ed James, 1956 Jul 26 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - The Quick and the Dead Clark E. Reynolds, 1956 Aug 2 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Rebuke Me Not Herbert Abbott Spiro, 1956 Aug 9 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Top Rung Reuben Bercovitch, 1956 Aug 23 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Miss Mabel R. C. Sherriff, 1956 Aug 30 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Mildred Pierce Benjamin Simcoe, 1956 Sep 20 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Now, Voyager Stanley Silverman, 1956 Oct 4 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Christmas in Connecticut Ed James, 1956 Dec 13 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - To Have and Have Not S. H. Barnett, 1957 Jan 17 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Vice Squad Paul Franklin, 1957 Jan 24 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - One Way Street S. H. Barnett, 1957 Feb 21 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Possessed Stanley H. Silverman, 1957 Feb 28 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Eileen Stanley Silverman, 1957 Mar 14 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - The Great Lie S. H. Barnett, 1957 Mar 21 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Adam Had Four Sons Paul Franklin, 1957 Apr 4 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - A House of His Own Loring D. Mandel, 1957 Apr 11 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - The Taggart Light Cecil Maiden, 1957 Apr 18 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - The Man Who Played God Paul Franklin, 1957 Apr 25 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - The Hard Way S. H. Barnett, 1957 May 2 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - The Armed Venus Richard P. McDonagh, 1957 May 23 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Payment in Kind John McGreevey, 1957 Jun 6 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Design for November S. H. Barnett, 1957 Jun 13 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Edge of Doubt Oliver Crawford, 1957 Jun 20 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - The Latch Key Paul Franklin, 1957 Jun 27 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Who is Picasso? Louis Pelletier, 1957 Jul 4 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Judge Not Stanley Silverman, 1957 Aug 15 (Box 221, Folder 2)